{"query": "crypto whale movements March 2026", "results": [{"title": "This Week in Crypto, Full Written Summary: W2 March 2026", "url": "https://app.santiment.net/insights/read/this-week-in-crypto-full-written-summary-w2-march-2026-10656", "snippet": "* **Whale Accumulation:** Key stakeholders (10-10k BTC wallets) are now accumulating, while retail traders continue to \"buy the dip,\" creating a complex market dynamic. * **Key Data:** S&P 500 is down ~2.2% over five weeks; Bitcoin is up 2.4%; Gold is up 3.7%. * **Key Data:** Bitcoin historically dropped 38-43% post-ATH, but recently gained 2.4% while the S&P slipped (chart). * **Key Data:** Key Stakeholders (10-10k BTC) shifted from dumping to accumulating two weeks ago. * **Actionable Tip:** Look for whale accumulation paired with retail capitulation (panic selling) for the highest probability buy signals. * **Key Data:** 10-10k BTC wallets control >66% of total supply and are net accumulating again (chart). * **Key Data:** 58.59 million non-zero BTC wallets (chart). Wallets holding 10k to 100k BTC show almost no correlation with price action. * **Key Data:** There are only ~84 wallets holding between 10k-100k BTC. * **Actionable Tip:** Long-term investors often look for negative yearly MVRV values to enter positions during periods of holder \"pain.\"."}, {"title": "$229M Unlock Events Ahead While Ethereum Whale Makes $17M Move", "url": "https://www.tradingview.com/news/coinpedia:e19f892dd094b:0-crypto-this-week-229m-unlock-events-ahead-while-ethereum-whale-makes-17m-move/", "snippet": "The crypto market is set for a large wave of token unlocks over the next seven days, with the total value expected to exceed $438 million, according to data from Tokenomist. Crypto analytics platform Top 7 Crypto reported that more than $229 million worth of tokens will be unlocked between March 16 and March 22, 2026. The largest release is expected from ASTER, which plans to unlock 78.4 million tokens worth approximately $55.9 million on March 17, representing about 0.98% of the tokenÆs total supply. Another notable unlock involves ZRO, the token associated with the LayerZero ecosystem, which will release $50.3 million worth of tokens on March 20. On the other hand, while token unlocks dominate the weekly schedule, blockchain data also shows large accumulation activity. **What are crypto token unlocks and why do they matter?**. More than $438 million worth of tokens are expected to unlock over the next seven days, adding new supply across multiple crypto projects."}, {"title": "What Crypto Whales Are Buying For Potential Gains In March 2026", "url": "https://finance.yahoo.com/news/crypto-whales-buying-potential-gains-170000216.html", "snippet": 
